{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032024351","data":{"timestamp":" 948032024351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032024980","data":{"timestamp":" 948032024979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032026055","data":{"timestamp":" 948032026054"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032026773","data":{"timestamp":" 948032026772"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032027703","data":{"timestamp":" 948032027702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUNA"," userResponse":" ALIVUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032028510","data":{"timestamp":" 948032028509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032029175","data":{"timestamp":" 948032029175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKUU"," userResponse":" VIKUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032029876","data":{"timestamp":" 948032029876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBANI"," userResponse":" SHAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032030480","data":{"timestamp":" 948032030479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032050635","data":{"timestamp":" 948032050635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032055588","data":{"timestamp":" 948032055588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032057008","data":{"timestamp":" 948032057007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032059497","data":{"timestamp":" 948032059496"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" START_ANANSI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032063540","data":{"timestamp":" 948032063540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032066054","data":{"timestamp":" 948032066053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUNA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032068755","data":{"timestamp":" 948032068754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUNA"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032070432","data":{"timestamp":" 948032070432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUNA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032071587","data":{"timestamp":" 948032071586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" ALIVUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032072584","data":{"timestamp":" 948032072584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032076690","data":{"timestamp":" 948032076690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKUU"," userResponse":" VIKUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032078913","data":{"timestamp":" 948032078913"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBANI"," userResponse":" START_SHAMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032082316","data":{"timestamp":" 948032082316"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBANI"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032083974","data":{"timestamp":" 948032083974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032085150","data":{"timestamp":" 948032085149"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032087578","data":{"timestamp":" 948032087576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIPENDEZA"," userResponse":" VILIPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032087803","data":{"timestamp":" 948032087802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032088804","data":{"timestamp":" 948032088803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONEKANA"," userResponse":" KUONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032089548","data":{"timestamp":" 948032089547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032090161","data":{"timestamp":" 948032090159"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032092299","data":{"timestamp":" 948032092298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIPENDEZA"," userResponse":" VILIPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032093409","data":{"timestamp":" 948032093409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032093420","data":{"timestamp":" 948032093420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONEKANA"," userResponse":" KUONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032093787","data":{"timestamp":" 948032093786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032094512","data":{"timestamp":" 948032094512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032096875","data":{"timestamp":" 948032096874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVICHOMA"," userResponse":" ALIVICHOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032098083","data":{"timestamp":" 948032098083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TARATIBU"," userResponse":" TARATIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032099020","data":{"timestamp":" 948032099020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032099819","data":{"timestamp":" 948032099818"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032100228","data":{"timestamp":" 948032100227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032101160","data":{"timestamp":" 948032101160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" AKAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032101769","data":{"timestamp":" 948032101768"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032104914","data":{"timestamp":" 948032104914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVICHOMA"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032106100","data":{"timestamp":" 948032106100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVICHOMA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032107886","data":{"timestamp":" 948032107885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVICHOMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032108214","data":{"timestamp":" 948032108214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TARATIBU"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032109252","data":{"timestamp":" 948032109252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TARATIBU"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032111100","data":{"timestamp":" 948032111099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TARATIBU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032112256","data":{"timestamp":" 948032112256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" START_KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032114365","data":{"timestamp":" 948032114365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032115818","data":{"timestamp":" 948032115817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032116811","data":{"timestamp":" 948032116810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032120173","data":{"timestamp":" 948032120173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032121821","data":{"timestamp":" 948032121821"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032125090","data":{"timestamp":" 948032125090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032127982","data":{"timestamp":" 948032127982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" AKAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032130209","data":{"timestamp":" 948032130209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032132818","data":{"timestamp":" 948032132817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDE"," userResponse":" PUNDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032132981","data":{"timestamp":" 948032132981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032133954","data":{"timestamp":" 948032133953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032134926","data":{"timestamp":" 948032134925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032135777","data":{"timestamp":" 948032135777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITIA"," userResponse":" AKITIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032136498","data":{"timestamp":" 948032136497"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TONGE"," userResponse":" TONGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032136693","data":{"timestamp":" 948032136692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032137263","data":{"timestamp":" 948032137263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032138378","data":{"timestamp":" 948032138377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYWANI"," userResponse":" KINYWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032139606","data":{"timestamp":" 948032139604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032140047","data":{"timestamp":" 948032140047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032141122","data":{"timestamp":" 948032141121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIBISHWA"," userResponse":" ULIBISHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032144921","data":{"timestamp":" 948032144921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDE"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032146480","data":{"timestamp":" 948032146480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDE"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032147787","data":{"timestamp":" 948032147786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032150045","data":{"timestamp":" 948032150045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032152964","data":{"timestamp":" 948032152964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" START_ANANSI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032154097","data":{"timestamp":" 948032154097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032156292","data":{"timestamp":" 948032156292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032158513","data":{"timestamp":" 948032158512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITIA"," userResponse":" AKITIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032161296","data":{"timestamp":" 948032161295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TONGE"," userResponse":" TONGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032162695","data":{"timestamp":" 948032162695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032164209","data":{"timestamp":" 948032164208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032167802","data":{"timestamp":" 948032167802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYWANI"," userResponse":" KINYWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032168809","data":{"timestamp":" 948032168808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" KINYWANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032172918","data":{"timestamp":" 948032172918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032174551","data":{"timestamp":" 948032174551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032177091","data":{"timestamp":" 948032177090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIBISHWA"," userResponse":" PUNDE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032178558","data":{"timestamp":" 948032178558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIBISHWA"," userResponse":" START_ULIBISHWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032180411","data":{"timestamp":" 948032180411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIBISHWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032182395","data":{"timestamp":" 948032182395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032183310","data":{"timestamp":" 948032183310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032184140","data":{"timestamp":" 948032184139"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOYONI"," userResponse":" MOYONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032186873","data":{"timestamp":" 948032186872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" TONGE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032191320","data":{"timestamp":" 948032191320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032195001","data":{"timestamp":" 948032195001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032201655","data":{"timestamp":" 948032201655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948032201760","data":{"timestamp":" 948032201760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000116_171256"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}